here's a short video to show you some of
这是一个简短的视频，向您展示一些
the new dev tool features that are
新的开发工具功能是
available in spring boot 1.3 I've got a
在 spring boot 1.3中可用
small demo application here it's just
小型演示应用程序就在这里
got one main method one controller sets
一种主要方法一套控制器
up some information in the model one CSS
在模型中的一些信息CSS
file and one HTML page this is rendered
文件和一个呈现的HTML页面
using time leaf if I start this
如果我开始使用时间叶
application and then head over to the
应用程序，然后转到
browser and refresh it you'll see we get
浏览器并刷新它，您将看到我们得到
a very simple page if you've ever used
一个非常简单的页面（如果您曾经使用过）
lattice you may recognize this kind of
你可能会认识到这种
style of application this is one of the
应用程序样式，这是
demo apps that ships with lattice I've
我附带的演示应用程序
just copied it to the spring so it's
刚复制到春天，所以
spring boot 1.2 if you wanted to
spring boot 1.2，如果你想
actually make changes to this
实际对此进行更改
application while it was running things
运行中的应用程序
were a little bit hit-and-miss so for
有点失误，所以
instance if I wanted to change the CSS
实例，如果我想更改CSS
maybe I changed the font size so it's a
也许我改变了字体大小，所以
bit smaller then that works but if I
有点小然后工作，但如果我
want to change the time leaf template by
想要通过更改时间叶模板
default that won't work so if I change
默认不起作用，所以如果我更改
maybe this just drop the ears refresh
也许这只是让耳朵刷新
the browser but the text here doesn't
浏览器，但此处的文本不
update this is because time leaf is
更新这是因为时间叶是
actually caching the result of this
实际缓存此结果
template parsing so it doesn't have to
模板解析，因此不必
do it every time and there's a property
每次都做，有一个属性
that you can set to change this but it's
您可以设置更改它，但这是
a bit awkward to have to remember to do
不得不记住要做的事有点尴尬
it when it comes to actually changing
当涉及到实际变化时
your Java code you're normally out of
您的Java代码通常不可用
luck entirely unless you're running in
除非运气好的话，否则完全运气
debug mode and just changing a single
调试模式，仅更改一个
method so we're spring boot 1.3 there's
方法，所以我们是Spring Boot 1.3，
a new module that you can add to your
您可以添加到您的新模块
pond file so if you add the spring boot
池塘文件，所以如果您添加 spring boot
dev tools module and then restart your
开发工具模块，然后重新启动
application you should find that it
应用程序，您应该会发现它
behaves slightly differently so once
表现略有不同，所以一旦
again I had over and refresh the page
我再次结束并刷新页面
this time if I change the the font size
这次如果我改变字体大小
in the CSS that continues to work as
在CSS中继续工作
before
之前
but I can also now change the template
但我现在也可以更改模板
and do that I can also this time change
做到这一点我也可以改变
the code so for instance let's add
代码，例如，让我们添加
something different in the amount of up
上升量有所不同
time
时间
what you'll notice here is that the
您会在这里注意到的是
spring application is actually detected
实际检测到春季申请
that the classifiers have changed
分类器已更改
beneath it and it's restarted itself so
在它下面并重新启动本身，因此
if I now refresh the browser I get that
如果现在刷新浏览器，我会得到
different message notice as well that
以及不同的消息通知
the restart time is a lot quicker than
重新启动时间比
the initial startup time this is because
初始启动时间是因为
everything's already loaded into the JVM
一切都已加载到JVM中
so we can just throw away classes that
所以我们可以扔掉那些
have changed but keep the majority of
已经改变但保留了大多数
the application already hot so it's much
该应用程序已经很热，所以很多
faster to startup this is quite nice but
更快启动，这是相当不错的，但是
clicking on this refresh button can get
点击此刷新按钮可以获取
a bit tedious after one so with spring
一个春天之后有点乏味
boot 1.3 we also include a live reload
开机1.3，我们还提供了实时重载
server this means you can get a plug-in
服务器，这意味着您可以获取插件
for your browser I've got got one
为您的浏览器，我有一个
installed here for Firefox if I click
如果我单击此处在Firefox上安装
this this plug-in will actually attach
这个插件实际上会附上
to my local machine then the next time
到下次我的本地机器
that I make a change and save the file I
我进行更改并保存文件
no longer have to refresh the browser it
不再需要刷新浏览器了
automatically does it for me and this
自动为我做这个
works with CSS files as well as Java
与CSS文件以及Java一起使用
files so if I make that font smaller
文件，所以如果我缩小字体
again it refreshes if I undo that and
如果我撤消它，它将再次刷新，并且
save the file again things go back to
再次保存文件，事情回到
usual
通常
so this makes the local development
所以这使得当地发展
experience a bit nicer but we've also
体验更好一点，但我们也
done some extra stuff to make the remote
做一些额外的东西，使遥控器
development experience nicer as well so
开发经验也更好
I've taken this application and I've
我已经拿了这个申请，我已经
actually packaged it up as a docker
实际上将其打包为docker
image and then published it to lattice
图片，然后将其发布到晶格
as a pushed application running on my
作为在我的计算机上运行的推送应用程序
local machine so here's the app running
本地计算机，所以这是运行的应用程序
within lattice within my docker
在我的泊坞窗内
environment within a local VM so one of
本地VM中的环境，因此
the problems with running apps within
在其中运行应用程序的问题
docker containers or with pushing them
码头工人容器或推动他们
to the cloud is that it can sometimes be
到云是有时
hard to actually attach a remote
很难实际连接遥控器
debugger to them so with 1.3 we've
为他们调试器，因此使用1.3
decided to add an additional feature
决定添加其他功能
where we can tunnel debug traffic
我们可以在其中隧道调试流量
through HTTP so to enable this you've
通过HTTP，因此要启用此功能
got to do a couple of things it's not on
必须做几件事
by default you've got it had a property
默认情况下，你有一个属性
to your application properties spring
您的应用程序属性Spring
dev tools remote secrets this is just a
开发工具远程机密这只是一个
password that's used to authenticate the
用于验证密码的密码
connection and then in the case of
连接，然后
docker you've got the additional
码头工人，你有额外的
arguments to actually start the JVM with
实际使用启动JVM的参数
debug mode so if you look at my docker
调试模式，所以如果你看我的码头工人
file if you go to the spring guide on
文件，如果你去Spring 指南
this you'll see that mine's got some
这你会看到我的有一些
additional things I've got ex debug and
我已经调试过的其他东西
I've got some configuration settings to
我有一些配置设置
say start as a server and don't suspend
说作为服务器启动，不要挂起
the application I don't actually need to
我实际上不需要的应用程序
specify the port this starts up one
指定要启动的端口之一
because Java will pick one and spring
因为Java将选一个
boots able to actually infer that so
靴子实际上可以推断出
with this application running I can now
有了这个应用程式，我现在可以
actually connect my local development
真正联系我的本地发展
environment to that remote application
该远程应用程序的环境
and do some remote debugging so to do
并做一些远程调试
that what you do is you have an
你要做的就是
additional run configuration so you
其他运行配置，因此您
create a run configuration that points
创建一个指向的运行配置
to your project as it usually would but
像往常一样进入您的项目，但是
rather than running your main method you
而不是运行您的主要方法
run a new main method that's part of
运行一个新的main方法，该方法是
spring boot so in this case I'm running
spring boot ，所以在这种情况下，我正在跑步
remote spring application I then also
远程Spring 应用我也
need to provide a single argument this
需要提供一个参数
is the URL of the end point that it's
是它的终点网址
actually going to hit so in this case
实际上要命中，所以在这种情况下
you can see it's the same you are
你可以看到你是一样的
I've got up in my browser so if I run
我已经在浏览器中启动，所以如果我运行
this application now you can see it
该应用程序现在您可以看到它
starts up fairly quickly and it's
启动相当快，它是
actually established a connection
实际建立了联系
through into my my docker image inside
进入我的docker映像
lattice if I want to actually attach now
如果我现在想实际附加
the remote debugger I can connect to my
我可以连接到我的远程调试器
local machine my local application here
本地机器我的本地应用程序在这里
this one that's running and this will
这个正在运行，这将
tunnel debug traffic through via HTTP to
通过HTTP隧道调试流量
talk to lattice so here I've got the
和格子说话，所以我在这里
remote debug setup if I connect you can
如果我连接，可以进行远程调试设置
see that I'm talking to an open JDK
看到我在和一个开放的JDK聊天
machine if i refresh this browser over
机器，如果我刷新此浏览器
here I'm going to hit a breakpoint that
在这里我要碰到一个断点
I've set up locally and you can see all
我已经在本地设置，您可以看到所有
the kind of regular debug stuff that you
您可以进行的常规调试工作
do that you'd normally you normally get
做到你通常会得到的
one thing to notice that this can be
要注意的一件事是
quite slow
相当慢
tunneling remote Deebo traffic which is
隧道远程Deebo交通是
quite chatty over HTTP is not
通过HTTP相当健谈不是
particularly fast so whilst it works
特别快，因此虽然有效
quite well on my lattice machine if I
如果我在格子机上表现很好
actually had this out on on the real
实际上是在现实中
internet it would be a little bit more
互联网会多一点
painful to use but it's still a
使用起来很痛苦，但仍然
potentially kind of useful technique
一种潜在的有用技术
I'll just let that run through the final
我只是让它贯穿最后
thing I want to show you is how we can
我想告诉你的是我们如何
use the same restart techniques on a
使用相同的重启技术
remote application so I'm going to take
远程应用程序，所以我要
this application that I've got here and
我在这里得到的这个应用程序
I'm going to rebuild it
我要重建它
and then I'm going to push it up to
然后我将其推升至
Cloud Foundry so the push process takes
Cloud Foundry，因此推送过程需要
a little while because it's gonna grab a
一会儿，因为它会抓住一个
JVM build up a an image file publish it
JVM建立一个映像文件并将其发布
start the application running so this
启动应用程序运行，这样
this kind of cycle can get a little bit
这种循环可能会有点
irritating if you're working on
烦人的如果你正在工作
something and you just want to make
有些东西，你只想做
small changes so we just give that a
小小的变化，所以我们给一个
minute or two to upload
一两分钟上传
and there we go if I head over to the
如果我前往
browser you see my applications running
浏览器中，您看到我的应用程序正在运行
and it's been up for 26 seconds so now
已经持续了26秒，所以现在
if I want to actually attach to that one
如果我想真正地附于那一个
I can do the same kind of technique as I
我可以做和我一样的技术
did before I've got another
在我得到另一个之前做了
configuration here and this time is
这里的配置，这次是
exactly the same but I'm pointing to the
完全一样，但我指的是
the Cloud Foundry endpoint so if I run
Cloud Foundry端点，所以如果我运行
that what's happening now is this
现在正在发生的事情是
application is connected to Clara
应用程序已连接到Clara
foundry but it's still monitoring my
铸造厂，但仍在监视我
local class path so if I want to make
本地课程路径，所以如果我想
changes now here so for instance if I
现在在这里更改，例如，如果我
change the font size again spring boots
再次更改字体大小
able to detect that change but this time
能够检测到这种变化，但这一次
rather than updating the local
而不是更新本地
application it will push it through to
应用程序将其推送到
the remote endpoint and then update
远程端点，然后更新
itself dynamically there and then
自己在那里动态地然后
refresh now if i refresh the browser you
如果我刷新浏览器，请立即刷新
can see it's updated we actually have
可以看到它实际上已经更新了
the live reload server still running
实时重新加载服务器仍在运行
locally as well so if I switch that on
在本地也是如此，如果我打开它
and change it back you can see it pushes
并改回它，你可以看到它的推动
the changes up and then triggers the
发生变化，然后触发
live reload so this is actually updating
实时重新加载，因此实际上正在更新
a remote service on the internet but
互联网上的远程服务，但是
refreshing my browser for me and this
为我刷新浏览器，这
works with with restarts as well so I
与重启一起工作，所以我
can change for design change the uptime
可以更改设计以更改正常运行时间
again if I save that application it's
再次，如果我保存该应用程序，
going to recompile it notice the change
要重新编译，请注意更改
push up the one class file that's
上推一个类文件
changed and then trigger a restart on
更改然后触发重新启动
Clara foundry thanks for watching
克拉拉铸造厂感谢您的观看